{
    "subject": "Barbara_Steele",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "James_Poe",
    "human_readable": "Barbara Steele is married to James Poe.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9673025012016296,
            "question": "Does a marriage exist between Barbara Steele and James Poe?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9270405173301697,
            "question": "To whom is Barbara Steele married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8393331170082092,
            "question": "Who is married to James Poe?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8155707716941833,
            "question": "Is Barbara Steele's marital status 'married'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8153157234191895,
            "question": "Name the husband of Barbara Steele."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7474278807640076,
            "question": "Who are Barbara Steele and James Poe connected by?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7006133794784546,
            "question": "Is Barbara Steele in a relationship?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5500819683074951,
            "question": "What is the name of James Poe's wife?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5290271043777466,
            "question": "What is the name of James Poe's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.32931673526763916,
            "question": "Who shares a marital bond with James Poe?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Barbara Steele is married to James Poe.",
            "html": "yago_5851_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of James Poe's spouse?",
            "html": "yago_5851_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of James Poe's wife?",
            "html": "yago_5851_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Barbara Steele in a relationship?",
            "html": "yago_5851_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5851_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5851_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5851_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5851_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5851_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5851_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5851_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5851_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5851_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5851_77.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON response:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents confirm that Barbara Steele was indeed married to screenwriter James Poe, from 1969 to 1978. This information is mentioned in multiple files (e.g., file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_5851/re-ranker-msmarco/36.txt and file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_5851/re-ranker-msmarco/77.txt)."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents clearly state that James Poe was married to actress Barbara Steele from 1969 to 1978, which directly supports the given triple."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n     \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}